VALENTINE KAL`CHEVSKI

FRONT-END DEVELOPER









ABOUT ME

Front-end developer with experience in creating SPA using React, Redux, HTML, CSS, JS./TS.

My free time is dedicated to Codewars programming tutorials and educational books. I'm expanding the horizon in back-end way. In the future I see myself as a Full Stack Developer.

I would like to find a project work/full-time job in a creative company with up-to-date tasks and collaborative team!

CONTACTS

MY PORTFOLIO CODEWARS PROFILE +375-25-732-18-33 valtikamore@gmail.com Minsk.Belarus

LANGUAGES

English pre-intermediate (in progress)

SKILLS

- React
- Redux
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Rest Api
- Formik
- HTML 5
- CSS 3, CSS-modules
- Material UI
- Unit-tests
- Storybook
- Git

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER, FREELANCE

February 2021 - Present

Creating apps using React and TypeScript, Redux state management and REST API.

Engaged in refactoring and bug fixing.

Cross-browser, adaptive, responsive development

Migration from JavaScript to TypeScript

Implemented flow-authorization, notification, forms (Formik and Redux-form).

Created Unit tests, Snapshot tests, component views in Storybook

INDIVIDUAL ENTREPRENEUR IN SALES

2016-2020

Superviced and trained employees

Conversation with suppliers and customers

Implementation of the sales plan, conducting price monitoring

EDUCATION

IT-INCUBATOR 2021

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT (REACT / REDUX / TYPESCRIPT)

Colledge Business and law 2013-2016

ECOMINIC AND COMMERCIALIZATION

Other:

UDEMI, HTML-ACADEMY, YOUTUBE

BOOKS : GROKKING ALGORITHMS, HEAD FIRST: HTML

CSS , JAVASCRIPT, YOU DON'T KNOW JS